- Do something about this.
This is stupid.
- Yo, turn it down, man!
Turn that noise down, man!
- Yo, what's up with his?
- Turn it down, boys!
Yo, turn it down, man.
- I know what to do.
- One, two, three, four.
♪ Now there's a backseat lover ♪
♪ That's always undercover ♪
♪ And I talk 'til my daddy say ♪
♪ Said you ain't seen nothin' ♪
♪ 'Til you're down on the muffin ♪
♪ And there's sure to
be a change in ways ♪
♪ Now there's a cheerleader ♪
♪ That's a real big pleaser ♪
♪ As far as I can reminisce ♪
♪ And the best thing of loving ♪
♪ Was her sister and her cousin ♪
♪ And it started with a
little kiss like this ♪
♪ See-saw swingin' ♪
♪ With the boys in school ♪
♪ And her feet was flyin' up in the air ♪
♪ Singin' Hey diddle diddle
with a kitty in the middle ♪
♪ And they swingin' like
it just don't care ♪
♪ So I took a big chance ♪
♪ At the high school dance ♪
♪ With a lady who was ready to play ♪
♪ It wasn't me she was foolin' ♪
♪ 'Cause she knew what was she was doin' ♪
♪ When she told me how to walk this way ♪
♪ She told me to ♪
♪ Walk this way ♪
♪ Talk this way ♪
♪ She told me to ♪
♪ Walk this way ♪
♪ Talk this way ♪
♪ Well just gimme a kiss ♪
♪ Ooh a-like this ♪
♪ School girl sleazy ♪
♪ With a classy kind of sassy ♪
♪ Little skirt hangin' way up her knee ♪
♪ There were three young ladies ♪
♪ In the school gym locker ♪
♪ And they find they were lookin' at D ♪
♪ I was high school loser ♪
♪ Never made it with a lady ♪
♪ 'Til the boys told
me somethin' I missed ♪
♪ That my next door neighbor ♪
♪ Had a daughter had a favor ♪
♪ And I gave the girl a
little kiss like this ♪
♪ See-saw swingin' ♪
♪ With the boys in school ♪
♪ With your feet was
flyin' up in the air ♪
♪ Singin' hey diddle diddle
with a kitty in the middle ♪
♪ I was swingin' like I didn't care ♪
♪ So I took a big chance ♪
♪ At the high school dance ♪
♪ With a missy who was ready to play ♪
♪ It wasn't me she was foolin' ♪
♪ When she knew what was she was doin' ♪
♪ When she told me how to walk this way ♪
♪ She told me to ♪
♪ Walk this way ♪
♪ Talk this way ♪
♪ She told me to ♪
♪ Walk this way ♪
♪ Talk this way ♪
♪ Like this ♪